Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from the Series She Males
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from the series She males
1990-1998
Bailey 5
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
28 v.; 17-18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Tri Cite/Star Distributors
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing, forced feminization, and other transgender activity.
Publisher for some later titles: Tri-Cite/Star Distributors.
Titles for issues 101-116 (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
All titles paperbound.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- She Males
  - Delicious Danielle, c1990; SM_101_ (Box 101-212)
  - Anatomy of a boy-girl, c1990; SM_102_ (Box 101-212)
  - Under her skirts, c1990; SM_103_ (Box 101-212)
    Scope and Contents
    Barcode/price label on front cover
  - Transvestite son, c1990 (first printing 1982); SM_104_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on top edge: 1501023560
  - Canaday, c1990; SM_105_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Needing it, c1990; SM_106_ (Box 101-212)
    Copy 2: Price label for store The Bedside Table on front cover, obscuring printed price info.
  - Night prowler, c1990; SM_107_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on top edge: 3301023560. Barcode label on back cover, partially obscuring text.
  - Serving sisters, c1990 (first printing 1983); SM_108_ (Box 101-212)
    Copy 2: Stamp on top edge: 3301023560. Barcode label on back cover, partially obscuring text
  - Charlotte, c1991; SM_109_ (Box 101-212)
  - Halfway Bobby, c1991; SM_110_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on bottom edge: CBD
  - Strange is fine, c1991; SM_111_ (Box 101-212)
  - The lady has balls, c1991 (first printing 1987); SM_112_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on bottom edge: SODI [?]
  - Carl's old buddy, c1991; SM_113_ (Box 101-212)
  - Sinful treatment, c1991; SM_114_ (Box 101-212)
  - TV in blue, c1991; SM_115_ (Box 101-212)
  - Her huge meat, c1991 (first printing 1986); SM_116_ (Box 101-212)
  - Serving sisters, c1998; SM_201_ (Box 101-212)
    Barcode/price label on front cover, partially obscuring ill.
  - Night prowler, c1998; SM_202_ (Box 101-212)
  - Canaday, c1998; SM_203_ (Box 101-212)
    Price label on front cover
  - Changing partners, c1998; SM_204_ (Box 101-212)
  - The lady has balls, c1998; SM_205_ (Box 101-212)
  - Strange is fine, c1998; SM_206_ (Box 101-212)
  - Halfway Bobby, c1998; SM_207_ (Box 101-212)
  - Charlotte, c1998; SM_208_ (Box 101-212)
  - Victoria, TV, c1998; SM_209_ (Box 101-212)
  - Corset and studs, c1998; SM_210_ (Box 101-212)
  - Shamed schoolboy, c1998; SM_211_ (Box 101-212)
    Inventory (?) label for Capitol on front cover, partially obscuring ill.
  - "Brenda's" big deal, c1998; SM_212_ (Box 101-212)
    Stamp on top edge: 50